A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Projects (Grants), RG 3, Subgroup 1 and Subgroup 2 FA005
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (Grants), 1947-1996; 3; 750 Cubic Feet
  - Projects (Grants), 1947-1989; 1
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc., 1977 February-May (Box 840, Folder 5060)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc., 1977-1979 (Box 840, Folder 5061)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc., 1979 July-August (Box 840, Folder 5062)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 840, Folder 5063)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 840, Folder 5064)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc., Tax Information, 1970-1982 (Box 840, Folder 5065)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, 1968-1970 (Box 840, Folder 5066)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, 1970 July-August (Box 841, Folder 5066A)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, 1971-1972 (Box 841, Folder 5067)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, 1972-1973 (Box 841, Folder 5068)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, 1973-1976 (Box 841, Folder 5069)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, 1976-1977 (Box 841, Folder 5070)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. - United Planned Parenthood Campaign, Tax Information, 1969-1976 (Box 841, Folder 5071)
    - Planned Parenthood of Westchester, Inc., 1972-1975 (Box 841, Folder 5072)
    - Planned Parenthood of Westchester, Inc., Tax Information, 1972-1975 (Box 841, Folder 5073)
    - Planning Foundation of America, 1964-1965 (Box 841, Folder 5074)
    - Planning Foundation of America, 1965-1968 (Box 842, Folder 5075)
    - Planning Foundation of America, 1970-1971 (Box 842, Folder 5076)
    - Playing to Win, Inc., 1981-1983 (Box 842, Folder 5077)
    - Playwrights Horizons, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 842, Folder 5078)
    - Playwrights Horizons, Inc., Tax Information, 1977 (Box 842, Folder 5079)
    - Poets and Writers, Inc., 1979 June-October (Box 842, Folder 5080)
    - Poets and Writers, Inc., 1979-1984 (Box 842, Folder 5081)
    - Poets and Writers, Inc., Tax Information, 1980 (Box 842, Folder 5082)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., 1946-1959 (Box 843, Folder 5083)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., 11/13/1959 (Box 843, Folder 5084)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 843, Folder 5085)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 843, Folder 5086)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 843, Folder 5087)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 843, Folder 5088)
    - Police Athletic League, Inc., Tax Information, 1970-1973 (Box 844, Folder 5089)
    - Police Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 844, Folder 5090)
    - Police Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 844, Folder 5091)
    - Police Foundation, 1977-1980 (Box 844, Folder 5092)
    - Police Foundation, Tax Information, 1970-1980 (Box 844, Folder 5093)
    - Policy Sciences Center, Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 844, Folder 5094)
    - Policy Sciences Center, Inc., 1980 February-December (Box 844, Folder 5095)
    - Policy Sciences Center, Inc., 1981 January 5 (Box 844, Folder 5096)
    - Policy Sciences Center, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 845, Folder 5097)
    - Policy Sciences Center, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 845, Folder 5098)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1955-1958 (Box 845, Folder 5099)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 845, Folder 5100)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 845, Folder 5101)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 845, Folder 5102)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 845, Folder 5103)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1968 February-May (Box 846, Folder 5104)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1967 September-December (Box 846, Folder 5105)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1969 February-November (Box 846, Folder 5106)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 846, Folder 5107)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 846, Folder 5108)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1971 April-August (Box 846, Folder 5109)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 847, Folder 5110)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1972 August-September (Box 847, Folder 5111)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 847, Folder 5112)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1974 March-June (Box 847, Folder 5113)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 847, Folder 5114)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 848, Folder 5115)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1976 December (Box 848, Folder 5116)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 848, Folder 5117)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 848, Folder 5118)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 848, Folder 5119)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1982 February-May (Box 849, Folder 5120)
    - Population Council, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 849, Folder 5121)
    - Population Education, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 849, Folder 5122)
    - Population Education, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 849, Folder 5123)
    - Population Education, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 849, Folder 5124)
    - Population Education, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 849, Folder 5125)
    - Population Education, Inc., Tax Information, 1974-1979 (Box 849, Folder 5126)
    - (The) Population Institute, 1970-1972 (Box 850, Folder 5127)
    - (The) Population Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 850, Folder 5128)
    - (The) Population Institute, 1974-1977 (Box 850, Folder 5129)
    - (The) Population Institute Tax Information, 1970-1972 (Box 850, Folder 5130)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1957 February-December (Box 850, Folder 5131)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 850, Folder 5132)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 850, Folder 5133)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1962 January-June (Box 851, Folder 5134)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 851, Folder 5135)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 851, Folder 5136)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 851, Folder 5137)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 851, Folder 5138)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1968 February-September (Box 852, Folder 5139)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 852, Folder 5140)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1970 March-October (Box 852, Folder 5141)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 852, Folder 5142)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1971 April-December (Box 852, Folder 5143)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1972 February-July (Box 852, Folder 5144)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 853, Folder 5145)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 853, Folder 5146)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 853, Folder 5147)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1975 May-September (Box 853, Folder 5148)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 853, Folder 5149)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 853, Folder 5150)
    - Population Reference Bureau, Inc., Tax Information, 1971-1973 (Box 853, Folder 5151)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1961-1969 (Box 854, Folder 5152)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1969-1975 (Box 854, Folder 5153)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 854, Folder 5154)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1978 September (Box 854, Folder 5155)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 854, Folder 5156)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1979 October-November (Box 855, Folder 5157)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 855, Folder 5158)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 855, Folder 5159)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1981 May 7 (Box 855, Folder 5160)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1981 May-December (Box 855, Folder 5161)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 856, Folder 5162)
    - (The) Potomac Institute, Inc., Tax Information, 1978-1982 (Box 856, Folder 5163)
    - Practicing Law Institute, 1964 July-December (Box 856, Folder 5164)
    - Practicing Law Institute, 1964-1976 (Box 856, Folder 5165)
    - Pratt Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 856, Folder 5166)
    - Pratt Institute, 1971-1972 (Box 856, Folder 5167)
    - Pratt Institute, 1972-1973 (Box 856, Folder 5168)
    - Pratt Institute, 1973-1974 (Box 857, Folder 5169)
    - Pratt Institute, 1974 November-December (Box 857, Folder 5170)
    - Pratt Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 857, Folder 5171)
    - Pratt Institute, 1976-1978 (Box 857, Folder 5172)
    - Pratt Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 857, Folder 5173)
    - Pratt Institute, 1979 April-September (Box 858, Folder 5174)
    - Pratt Institute, 1980-1981 (Box 858, Folder 5175)
    - Pratt Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 858, Folder 5176)
    - Pratt Institute, 1983 May-December (Box 858, Folder 5177)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1962-1963 (Box 858, Folder 5178)
    - Pratt Institute, 1980 February 29 (Box 858A, Folder 5175A)
    - Pratt Institute, March 29, 1982 (Box 858A, Folder 5176A)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1963-1964 (Box 859, Folder 5179)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1965 April 6; 2 copies. (Box 859, Folder 5180)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1965 April-June (Box 859, Folder 5181)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1965 June-November (Box 859, Folder 5182)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1965-1966 (Box 859, Folder 5183)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1966 March-December (Box 860, Folder 5184)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1967 (Box 860, Folder 5185)
    - Pratt Institute - School of Architecture, 1969 (Box 860, Folder 5186)
    - Prince Edward Free School Association, 1963-1964 (Box 860, Folder 5187)
    - Princeton Education Center at Blairstown, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 860, Folder 5188)
    - Princeton Education Center at Blairstown, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 860, Folder 5189)
    - Princeton Education Center at Blairstown, Inc. Tax Information, 1976-1981 (Box 860, Folder 5190)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary, 1962 (Box 861, Folder 5191)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary, 1972-1976 (Box 861, Folder 5192)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary, 1977-1984 (Box 861, Folder 5193)
    - Princeton Theological Seminary, Tax Information, 1972-1984 (Box 861, Folder 5194)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 861, Folder 5195)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1977 March-December (Box 861, Folder 5196)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1977 December-1978 (Box 861, Folder 5197)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 862, Folder 5198)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1980 January-November (Box 862, Folder 5199)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1981-1984 (Box 862, Folder 5200)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1984 March-December (Box 862, Folder 5201)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1984-1985 (Box 862, Folder 5202)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1985 February-October (Box 863, Folder 5203)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1985 December (Box 863, Folder 5204)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1986 January-September (Box 863, Folder 5205)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 863, Folder 5206)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1987 January-July (Box 863, Folder 5207)
    - Princeton University - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1987 August-October (Box 863, Folder 5208)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 1/22/1980 (Box 864, Folder 5209)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 1/22/1980 (Box 864, Folder 5210)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 1980-1981 (Box 864, Folder 5211)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 4/8/1981 (Box 864, Folder 5212)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 5/8/1981 (Box 864, Folder 5213)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 1981 June-December (Box 865, Folder 5214)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 1982 March-June (Box 865, Folder 5215)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 6/9/1982 (Box 865, Folder 5216)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, 1982-1983 (Box 865, Folder 5217)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 865, Folder 5218)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, Publications, 1981-1982 (Box 866, Folder 5219)
    - Princeton University - Princeton Urban and Regional Research Center, Publications, 1982 March-June (Box 866, Folder 5220)
    - Private Agencies Collaborating Together, Inc. (PACT), 1973-1980 (Box 866, Folder 5221)
    - Private Agencies Collaborating Together, Inc. (PACT), 1980-1982 (Box 866, Folder 5222)
    - Private Agencies Collaborating Together, Inc. (PACT), 1982-1983 (Box 866, Folder 5223)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1971-1978 (Box 866, Folder 5224)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1978-1979 (Box 867, Folder 5225)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1979 June (Box 867, Folder 5226)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1979 July-December (Box 867, Folder 5227)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1980 January-May (Box 867, Folder 5228)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1980 May-December (Box 867, Folder 5229)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1981 February-December (Box 868, Folder 5230)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1982 February-December (Box 868, Folder 5231)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1983 March-April (Box 868, Folder 5232)
    - Procedural Aspects of International Law Institute, The, 1983 May-December (Box 868, Folder 5233)
    - Project for Public Spaces, The, 1977-1979 (Box 868, Folder 5234)
    - Project for Public Spaces, The, 1979-1981 (Box 868, Folder 5235)
    - Prospect School, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 869, Folder 5236)
    - Prospect School, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 869, Folder 5237)
    - Prospect School, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 869, Folder 5238)
    - Prospect School, Inc., 1977 February-March (Box 869, Folder 5239)
    - Prospect School, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 869, Folder 5240)
    - Prospect School, Inc., 1978 August (Box 870, Folder 5241)
    - Prospect School, Inc., Tax Information, 1973-1980 (Box 870, Folder 5242)
    - Prospect School, Inc., Teachers Centers in the Context of Open Education, 1974 October-November (Box 870, Folder 5243)
    - Protestant Fund of Greater New York, Inc., 1947 (Box 870, Folder 5244)
    - Public Education Association, 1942-1950 (Box 870, Folder 5245)
    - Public Education Association, 1950-1952 (Box 870, Folder 5246)
    - Public Education Association, 1952-1955 (Box 870, Folder 5247)
    - Public Education Association, 1955-1958 (Box 871, Folder 5248)
    - Public Education Association, 1959-1960 (Box 871, Folder 5249)
    - Public Education Association, 1961-1963 (Box 871, Folder 5250)
    - Public Education Association, 1964 June-July (Box 871, Folder 5251)
    - Public Education Association, 1964-1965 (Box 871, Folder 5252)
    - Public Education Association, 1966-1968 (Box 871, Folder 5253)
    - Public Education Association, 1968-1969 (Box 872, Folder 5254)
    - Public Education Association, 1969-1970 (Box 872, Folder 5255)
    - Public Education Association, 1970 October-December (Box 872, Folder 5256)
    - Public Education Association, 1971-1972 (Box 872, Folder 5257)
    - Public Education Association, 1972-1973 (Box 872, Folder 5258)
    - Public Education Association, 1973-1975 (Box 872, Folder 5259)
    - Public Education Association, 1975-1976 (Box 873, Folder 5260)
    - Public Education Association, 1976 September-December (Box 873, Folder 5261)
    - Public Education Association, 1977-1978 (Box 873, Folder 5262)
    - Public Education Association, 1978 January (Box 873, Folder 5263)
    - Public Education Association, 1978 January-September (Box 873, Folder 5264)
    - Public Education Association, 1979-1982 (Box 873, Folder 5265)
    - Public Education Association, Tax Information, 1970-1977 (Box 874, Folder 5266)
    - Puerto Rican Association for Community Affairs, Inc. Tax Information, 1973-1977 (Box 874, Folder 5267)
    - Puerto Rican Association for Community Affairs, Inc., 1975-1978 (Box 874, Folder 5268)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., 1960-1963 (Box 874, Folder 5269)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., 1963-1965 (Box 874, Folder 5270)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., 1965 January-June (Box 874, Folder 5271)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 874, Folder 5272)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 874, Folder 5273)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 875, Folder 5274)
    - Puerto Rican Forum, Inc., Tax information, 1969-1971 (Box 875, Folder 5275)
    - Puerto Rican Guidance Center, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 875, Folder 5276)
    - Puerto Rican Guidance Center, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 875, Folder 5277)
    - Puerto Rican Guidance Center, Inc., Tax Information, 1968-1970 (Box 875, Folder 5278)
    - Puerto Rican Institute for Social Research, 1973-1975 (Box 875, Folder 5279)
    - Puerto Rican Institute for Social Research, 12/11/1975 (Box 875, Folder 5280)
    - Puerto Rican Institute for Social Research, 1975-1976 (Box 875, Folder 5281)
    - Puerto Rican Institute for Social Research, 1976-1978 (Box 875, Folder 5282)
    - Puerto Rican Institute for Social Research Tax Information, 1974-1975 (Box 876, Folder 5283)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 876, Folder 5284)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1972-1974 (Box 876, Folder 5285)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 876, Folder 5286)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 876, Folder 5287)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 4/30/1976 (Box 877, Folder 5288)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 877, Folder 5289)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1977 January-April (Box 877, Folder 5290)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 877, Folder 5291)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1978 July-September (Box 877, Folder 5292)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1979 (Box 877, Folder 5293)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 878, Folder 5294)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1981-1983 (Box 878, Folder 5295)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, Tax Information, 1969-1982 (Box 878, Folder 5296)
    - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Co., 1980-1981 (Box 878, Folder 5297)
    - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Co., 1981-1983 (Box 878, Folder 5298)
    - (The) Push Foundation, 1976 June-August (Box 878, Folder 5299)
    - (The) Push Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 878, Folder 5300)
    - (The) Push Foundation, 1978-1983 (Box 879, Folder 5301)
    - (The) Push Foundation Tax Information, 1976-1984 (Box 879, Folder 5302)
    - (The) Quaker Committee on Social Rehabilitation, Inc., 1963-1970 (Box 879, Folder 5303)
    - (The) Quaker Committee on Social Rehabilitation, Inc., 1970-1976 (Box 879, Folder 5304)
    - (The) Quaker Committee on Social Rehabilitation, Inc. Tax Information, 1970 (Box 879, Folder 5305)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1972-1978 (Box 879, Folder 5306)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 879, Folder 5307)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 879, Folder 5308)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 880, Folder 5309)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1984 May 19-December (Box 880, Folder 5310)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1985 January-June (Box 880, Folder 5311)
    - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Inc., 1985 June-December (Box 880, Folder 5312)
    - Queen Wilhelmina Fund, 1942 (Box 880, Folder 5313)
    - Queens Federation of Youth Organizations, Inc. Tax Information, 1975-1978 (Box 880, Folder 5314)
    - Queens Federation of Youth Organizations, Inc., 1974-1980 (Box 880, Folder 5315)
    - Queens University, 1964-1971 (Box 880, Folder 5316)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute, formerly: The Radcliffe Institute for Independent Research Study, 1955-1963 (Box 881, Folder 5317)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute, 1963-1965 (Box 881, Folder 5318)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute, 1965-1969 (Box 881, Folder 5319)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute, 1968-1969 (Box 881, Folder 5320)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute, 1969-1972 (Box 881, Folder 5321)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute, 1972-1975 (Box 881, Folder 5322)
    - (The) Radcliffe College - Radcliffe Institute. Tax Information, 1970-1975 (Box 881, Folder 5323)
    - (The) Real Great Society, Inc., 1966-1969 (Box 882, Folder 5324)
    - Recording for the Blind, Inc., 1954-1958 (Box 882, Folder 5325)
    - Recording for the Blind, Inc., 1958-1964 (Box 882, Folder 5326)
    - Recording for the Blind, Inc., 1964-1969 (Box 882, Folder 5327)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 882, Folder 5328)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1951-1954 (Box 882, Folder 5329)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1955 January-November (Box 883, Folder 5330)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1955-1956 (Box 883, Folder 5331)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 883, Folder 5332)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 883, Folder 5333)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1959 (Box 883, Folder 5334)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1960 January-April (Box 884, Folder 5335)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1960-1961 (Box 884, Folder 5336)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 884, Folder 5337)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1962 March-April (Box 884, Folder 5338)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 884, Folder 5339)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1963 August-December (Box 884, Folder 5340)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 885, Folder 5341)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1965 June-December (Box 885, Folder 5342)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1966 March-September (Box 885, Folder 5343)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 885, Folder 5344)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1967 January-May (Box 885, Folder 5345)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 885, Folder 5346)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 886, Folder 5347)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 886, Folder 5348)
    - Regional Plan Association, Inc., 1971 January-April (Box 886, Folder 5349)